A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.32 (A2006) FA483
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2006.042: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1998-2004; AC.2006.042; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3791-R3792; 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3791-R3792.
  - Special Programs (SP), AC.2006.042.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2001 SP 214 - PHILADELPHIA TABERNACLE PENTECOSTAL CHURCH (CANADA) - EMERGENCY SERVICES, 2001-2002 (Box R3792)
    - 2001 SP 302 - (GLOBAL PHILANTHROPY) - GIVINGWELL PROJECT, 2000-2001 (Box R3792)
    - 2001 SP 502 - SEIU EDUCATION AND SUPPORT FUND - OUTREACH AND COMMUNICATION FOR IMMIGRANT WORKERS AFFECTED BY THE WTC ATTACK, 2001-2004 (Box R3792)
  - Working Communities (WC), AC.2006.042.4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2001 WC 041 - CENTER ON BUDGET AND POLICY PRIORITIES - JOB CREATION PROGRAMS FOR WELFARE RECIPIENTS, 2001-2002 (Box R3792)
    - 2001 WC 045 - INSTITUTE ON TAXATION AND ECONOMIC POLICY - TAX REFORM AND POOR FAMILIES; JOB CREATION AND ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT SUBSIDIES, 2001-2003 (Box R3792)
    - 2001 WC 050 - BRITISH CONSULATE-GENERAL - UK W'ORKFORCE DEVELOPMENT PILOT STAFF EXCHANGE INITIATIVE, 2001-2004 (Box R3792)
    - 2001 WC 056 - AMERICAN ASSOCIATION OF STATE COLLEGES AND UNIVERSITIES - WORKSHOP ON STANDARDIZED TESTS PREPARATION FOR PROSPECTIVE TEACHERS (Box R3792)
    - 2001 WC 085 - (WORKING COMMUNITIES) - FUTURE OF WORK MULTl-AUTHORED VOLUME (Box R3792)
    - 2001 WC 087 - MS. FOUNDATION FOR WOMEN - "RAISE THE FLOOR" MEDIA CAMPAIGN, 2001-2003 (Box R3792)
    - 2001 WC 105 - INSTITUTE OF EDUCATIONAL LEADERSHIP, INC. - COMMUNITY BUILDING AND EDUCATION REFORM AT LOCAL LEVEL, 1998-2002 (Box R3792)
    - 2001 WC 107 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (RIVERSIDE) - CONFERENCE ON TRANSNATIONAL LIVES OF OAXACAN WOMEN, 2001-2003 (Box R3792)
    - 2001 WC 108 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (IRVINE) - "RESHAPING THE AMERICAS" CONFERENCE, 2000-2003 (Box R3792)
    - 2001 WC 109 - CITY COLLEGE, CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - CONFERENCE, "THE TRANSNATIONALIZATION OF EVERYDAY LIFE", 2001-2004 (Box R3792)
    - 2001 WC 111 - INSTITUTE FOR PUBLIC POLICY RESEARCH (ENGLAND) - BC CONFERENCE: GOOD CITIZEN, GOOD STATE: WHAT IS PROGRESSIVE POLITICS FOR?, 2001-2004 (Box R3792)
- AC.2006.050: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1998-2005; AC.2006.050; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3793-R3798.; 6 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3793-R3798.
  - Africa Regional (AR), AC.2006.050.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - 2001 AR 001 - TEMU ANNA ANDREW - ACA: MARKET LIBERALIZATION WITHIN COFFEE INDUSTRY IN TANZANIA, 1999-2003 (Box R3793)
    - 2001 AR 005 - CHIMEDZA, ROBERT - ACA: SPECIAL EDUCATION TEACHERS IN ZIMBABWE, 2000-2002 (Box R3793)
    - 2001 AR 008 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - URBAN INTEGRATION SURVEY, 2000-2002 (Box R3793)
    - 2001 AR 016 - MULAA, MARGARET A. 0. - ACA: INTEGRATED PEST MANAGEMENT TECHNOLOGIES FOR VEGETABLES IN KENYA, 1999-2003 (Box R3793)
    - 2001 AR 018 - OTIENO, JUDITH AWINO - DROPOUT RATES AMONG PRIMARY SCHOOL GIRLS IN MARIGAT, KENYA, 2001-2002 (Box R3793)
    - 2001 AR 024 - INTERNATIONAL POTATO CENTER (PERU) - NUTRITION WORKSHOP, 2001-2004 (Box R3793)
    - 2001 AR 026 - INDEPTH NETWORK (GHANA) - NETWORK STRATEGIC PLANNING AND MEETING, 2000-2003 (Box R3793)
    - 2001 AR 029 - SOCIAL SCIENCE ACADEMY OF NIGERIA - NIGERIAN UNIVERSITY CASE STUDY, 2001-2004 (Box R3793)
    - 2001 AR 030 - (AFRICA REGIONAL) - PRIVATE-PUBLIC PARTNERSHIPS FOR SOCIAL DEVELOPMENT IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2001-2004 (Box R3793)
    - 2001 AR 036 - MANGISONI, JULIUS HEAVENOR - ACA: SOIL EROSION CONTROL TECHNOLOGIES IN MALAWI, 2001-2002 (Box R3793)
    - 2001 AR 037 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - MINDS ACROSS AFRICA SCHOOL CLUBS PROGRAM IN FOUR DISTRICTS, 2001-2002 (Box R3793)
    - 2001 AR 040 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - QUEST DIALOQUE WITH PRIVATE AND PUBLIC SECTORS, 2001-2002 (Box R3793)
    - 2001 AR 044 - KENYA - EDUCATION, SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY (MINISTRY OF) - WORKSHOP ON GUIDANCE AND COUNSELLING, 2001-2003 (Box R3794)
    - 2001 AR 045 - UNIVERSITY OF SUSSEX (ENGLAND) - IMPACT OF HIV/AIDS ON PRIMARY EDUCATION IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 1999-2002 (Box R3794)
    - 2001 AR 049 - POPULATION COUNCIL - ESTABLISH CENTER FOR POPULATION POLICY RESEARCH IN NAIROBI, 1994-2004; 2 folders. (Box R3794)
    - 2001 AR 053 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - MINDS ACROSS AFRICA SCHOOL CLUBS PROJECT, 1998-2003 (Box R3794)
    - 2001 AR 054 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - REVIEW OF LEGAL ISSUES, 2001-2002 (Box R3794)
    - 2001 AR 061 - AFRICAN CAPACITY BUILDING FOUNDATION (ZIMBABWE) - PAN-AFRICAN CAPACITY-BUILDING FORUM, 2000-2004 (Box R3794)
    - 2001 AR 067 - CENTRE FOR HIGHER EDUCATION TF)ANSFORMATION TRUST (SOUTH AFRICA) - STRATEGIC COOPERATION SCENARIOS IN EASTERN CAPE, 2001-2002 (Box R3794)
    - 2001 AR 069 - NATIONAL COUNCIL FOR TERTIARY EDUCATION (GHANA) - TRANSFORMATION IN GHANA'S UNIVERSITIES, 2001-2004 (Box R3795)
    - 2001 AR 085 - INSTITUTE OF POLICY ANALYSIS AND RESEARCH (KENYA) - CONFERENCE ON AFRICAN CIVIL SOCIETY, 2001-2004 (Box R3795)
    - 2002 AR 001 - New School University - Democracy and Diversity Institute, 2001-2003 (Box R3795)
    - 2002 AR 009 - UNIVERSITY OF CAPE TOWN (SOUTH AFRICA) - CONFERENCE ON DEVELOPMENT ISSUES IN THE NEW ECONOMY, 2001-2003 (Box R3795)
    - 2002 AR 015 - WOMEN'S UNIVERSITY IN AFRICA TRijST (ZIMBABWE) - CONSULTATIVE MEETINGS FOR WOMEN'S UNIVERSITY, 2001-2003 (Box R3795)
    - 2002 AR 018 - MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY - KONARE - VISITING PROFESSOR (Box R3795)
      RESCINDED
  - Assets and Capacities (AC), AC.2006.050.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2002 AC 101 - (ASSETS & CAPACITIES) - COMMUNICATION FOR SOCIAL CHANGE - PUBLIC EDUCATION PROJECT ON GLOBALIZATION (Box R3793)
    - 2002 AC 104 - NATIONAL PUBLIC RADIO - SPECIAL NEWS COVERAGE AFTER 9/11 ATTACKS, 2001-2002 (Box R3793)
    - 2002 AC 202 - SCHOOL OF ORIENTAL AND AFRICAN STUDIES, UNIVERSITY OF LONDON (ENGLAND) - EXHIBITION OF WORKS OF HIROJI KUBOTA AND JOHN VINK, 2002-2003 (Box R3793)
    - 2002 AC 209 - SYNERGOS INSTITUTE - "UNIVERSITY FOR A NIGHT" EVENT, 2002-2003 (Box R3793)
    - 2002 AC 210 - EARTH TIMES FOUNDATION - GENERA, 2002-2005 (Box R3793)
  - Creativity and Culture (CC), AC.2006.050.3; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - 2000 CC 026 - UNIVERSITY OF COLORADO (BOULDER) - EXHIBITION, "VIETNAMESE LACQUER PAINTING - A NEW AGE", 2000-2002 (Box R3795)
    - 2000 CC 068 - UNIVERSITY OF MASSACHUSETTS (AMHERST) - "2050 PROJECT", 2000-2003 (Box R3795)
    - 2000 CC 069 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - 'HARRIET TUBMAN: A JOURNEY TO THE SOUTH", 2000-2003 (Box R3795)
    - 2000 CC 093 - LOCATION ONE - ART/NET LAB, 1998-2001 (Box R3795)
      Special Format items have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
      - Selected Events and Exhibitions, 1998-2001; 2006:050:001; Digital
      - Keith Sonnier O2 = O3, Fractured Oxygen = Ozone, 2001 September 20-November 28; 2006:050:002
    - 2000 CC 117 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - PROGAM ON CULTURE, CREATIVITY AND INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY, 2000-2004 (Box R3795)
    - 2000 CC 125 - THE DRAWING CENTER - EXHIBITION, "ANA MARIA MAIOLINO", 2000-2002 (Box R3795)
    - 2000 CC 133 - LEONARDO - "A-LIFE ART" AND "GENERATIVE SYSTEMS" PROJECTS, 2000-2003 (Box R3795)
    - 2000 CC 134 - ART INSTITUTE OF CHICAGO - DISTRIBUTION OF "FRAMES OF REFERENCE" EXHIBITION, 2000-2002 (Box R3795)
    - 2000 CC 138 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - COLLECTIVE MEMORY IN SOUTH AMERICA, 1999-2003 (Box R3796)
    - 2000 CC 138 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - COLLECTIVE MEMORY IN SOUTH AMERICA - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1999-2003 (Box R3796)
    - 2000 CC 140 - FOUNDATION FOR THE STUDY OF INDEPENDENT SOCIAL IDEAS - SPECIAL ISSUE OF DISSENT MAGAZINE: "THE NEW KILLING FIELDS", 2000-2003 (Box R3796)
    - 2000 CC 145 - AMERICAN LIBRARY ASSOCIATION - FORUM ON DIGITAL TECHNOLOGY AND FUTURE OF LIBRARIES, 2000-2002 (Box R3796)
    - 2000 CC 149 - GRADUATE SCHOOL AND UNIVERSITY CENTER, CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - INTERNATIONAL RESOURCE NETWORK PROJECT, 2000-2003 (Box R3796)
    - 2000 CC 154 - CORCORAN GALLERY OF ART - CANVAS PROJECT FOR AT-RISK YOUTH IN WASHINGTON D.C., 2000-2005 (Box R3796)
    - 2000 CC 155 - ARAB COMMUNITY CENTER FOR ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL SERVICES - VOICES FROM ARAB DETROIT PROJECT, 2001-2003 (Box R3796)
    - 2000 CC 156 - PEN AMERICAN CENTER - STRATEGIC PLANNING AND CAPACITY BUILDING, 2000-2004 (Box R3796)
    - 2001 CC 011 - LIEM, DEANN BORSHAY - DOCUMENTARY, "INTO THE ARMS OF STRANGERS", 2001-2003 (Box R3796)
    - 2001 CC 013 - HATTA, KAYO - "RAW FISH", 2001-2004 (Box R3796)
    - 2001 CC 015 - KOBLAND, KEN - FILM ON SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY'S POTENTIAL FOR MANKIND, 2001-2003 (Box R3796)
    - 2001 CC 016 - LUCIER, MARY - "GHOST TOWNS (THE EMPTYING OF THE PLAINS)", 2001-2004 (Box R3796)
    - 2001 CC 017 - MAYNOR, MELINDA - "LABORS OF LOVE: LUMBEE INDIAN ART & WORK", 2001-2004 (Box R3796)
    - 2001 CC 018 - McKAY, JIM - FILM, "ON THE WAY OUT", 2001-2003 (Box R3796)
    - 2001 CC 019 - RADTKE, EDWARD A - FILM ABOUT JUVENILE FELONS, 2001-2005 (Box R3796)
    - 2001 CC 020 - SACHS, LYNNE - EXPERIMENTAL DOCUMENTARY, "INVESTIGATION OF THE FLAME", 2001-2002 (Box R3796)
    - 2001 CC 021 - SCHNEEMAN, CAROLEE - VIDEO INSTALLATION, "TRANSPORT", 2001-2003 (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 022 - SORENSEN, VIBEKE - INTERACTIVE INSTALLATION, "SANCTUARY", 2001-2004 (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 023 - TRAN, KIM-TRANG - EXPERIMENTAL FILM, "CALL ME SUGAR", 2001-2002 (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 024 - VALDEZ, KINAN AND ANAHUAC - FILM, "BALLAD OF A SOLDIER", 2001-2004 (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 025 - RIOS, JOSE BUil - DOCUMENTARY, "LOS CRIMENES DE MAR DEL NORTE (THE NORTH SEA CRIMES)" (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 026 - CONSTANTINI, ARCANGEL - "DE LO POPULAR A LO ELECTRONICO (FROM THE POPULAR TO THE ELECTRONIC)", 2001-2004 (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 030 - MINT MUSEUM OF ART - "THE SPORT OF LIFE AND DEATH: THE MESOAMERICAN BALLGAME", 2000-2002 (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 032 - EXHIBITIONS INTERNATIONAL - "TESTIMONY: VERNACULAR ART OF THE AFRICAN-AMERICAN SOUTH", 2000-2002 (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 034 - MUSEUM OF CONTEMPORARY ART - EXHIBITION OF WORKS OF WILLIAM KENTRIDGE, 2000-2003 (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 035 - MONGOL-AMERICAN CULTURAL ORGANIZATION - FESTIVAL OF MONGOLIA 2001, 2001-2002 (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 037 - OPERA AMERICA - THE OPERA FUND, 2001-2002 (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 039 - CONSERVANCY FOR TIBETAN ART AND CULTURE - COMMUNITY NEEDS ASSESSMENT, 2001-2002 (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 040 - UNIVERSITY OF THE PHILIPPINES, DILIMAN - SYMPOSIUM, "A SEARCH IN ASIA FOR A NEW THEORY OF MUSIC", 2001-2002 (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 041 - SRI INTERNATIONAL - "INTERLINK" PROJECT, 2001-2003 (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 043 - NATIONAL INDIAN TELECOMMUNICATIONS INITIATIVE - VIRTUAL MUSEUM, 2001-2002 (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 044 - HARVESTWORKS - ROBOTIC ORCHESTRA COLLECTIVE, 2001-2003 (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 049 - LINCOLN CENTER THEATER - "THE OPHAN OF CHAO" ' (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 050 - NEW YORK CHAMBER SYMPHONY - "NEW MUSIC COMPETITION", 2001-2003 (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 051 - NATIONAL PERFORMANCE NETWORK - ARTISTS RETREATS, 2001-2002 (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 054 - HIP HOP THEATRE JUNCTION - SECOND ANNUAL FESTIVAL, 2000-2003 (Box R3797)
    - 2001 CC 056 - LEONARDO OBSERVATORY FOR THE ARTS AND TECHNO-SCIENCES (FRANCE) - "VIRTUAL AFRICA" AND "PIONEERS AND PATHBREAKERS" PROJECTS, 2001-2002 (Box R3798)
    - 2001 CC 058 - NORTH CAROLINA CENTRAL UNIVERSITY - EXHIBITION, "MALVIN GRAY JOHNSON: MODERN PAINTER", 2000-2002 (Box R3798)
    - 2001 CC 059 - MUSEUM OF FINE ARTS, HOUSTON - EXHIBITION OF SPANISH ART, 2000-2002 (Box R3798)
    - 2001 CC 062 - INSTITUTE OF ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL DEVELOPMENT (ARGENTINA) - CONVENING OF HUMANITIES RESIDENCY SITE LEADERS, "CRITICAL AGENDAS IN LATIN AMERICA", 2001-2002 (Box R3798)
    - 2001 CC 067 - MEM ASSOCIATES, INC. - "CHRONICLE OF THE ARTS", 2001-2003 (Box R3798)
    - 2001 CC 070 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (IRVINE) - WORKSHOPS ON DIGITAL CULTURE, 2001-2002 (Box R3798)
    - 2001 CC 072 - NEW HAVEN INTERNATIONAL FESTIVAL OF ARTS & IDEAS - 2001 INTERNATIONAL FESTIVAL, 2001-2002 (Box R3798)
    - 2001 CC 073 - BLUE STAR ART SPACE - EXHIBITION, "CELIA ALVAREZ MUNOZ: A SURVEY RETROSPECTIVE", 2000-2002 (Box R3798)
    - 2001 CC 074 - BRONX MUSEUM OF THE ARTS - EXHIBITION ON HIP HOP AND CONTEMPORARY ART, 2000-2002 (Box R3798)
    - 2001 CC 077 - INSTITUTE OF ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL DEVELOPMENT (ARGENTINA) - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS IN THE HUMANITIES, 1996-2002 (Box R3798)
    - 2001 CC 078 - CALIFORNIA NEWSREEL - PUBLIC TELEVISION SERIES, "AFRICA IN THE PICTURE...", 2001-2003 (Box R3798)
- AC.2006.053: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1999-2004; AC.2006.053; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, Box R3799.; 1 standard record storage box, Box R3799.
  - Creativity and Culture (CC), AC.2006.053.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2001 CC 079 - QUEENS MUSEUM OF ART - "TRANSLATED ACTS", 1999-2002 (Box R3799)
    - 2001 CC 080 - CANADIAN CONFERENCE OF THE ARTS (CANADA) - CONFERENCE ON INTERNATIONAL NETWORK FOR CULTURAL DIVERSITY, 2001-2002 (Box R3799)
    - 2001 CC 081 - DOCUMENTA 11 (GERMANY)"CREOLITE AND CREOLIZATION, 2000-2004 (Box R3799)
    - 2001 CC 085 - WBEZ ALLIANCE, INC. - THIRD COAST INTERNATIONAL AUDIO FESTIVAL (Box R3799)
    - 2001 CC 088 - AMERICAN FILM INSTITUTE - DIGITAL ARTS WORKSHOP, 2001-2002 (Box R3799)
    - 2001 CC 090 - NATYA DANCE THEATRE - CONFERENCE, "BHARATANATYAM IN THE DIASPORA", 2001-2002 (Box R3799)
    - 2001 CC 094 - AMERICAN CRAFT MUSEUM - EXHIBITION, "CHANGING HANDS: NATIVE AMERICAN ARTS TODAY", 2001-2003 (Box R3799)
    - 2001 CC 096 - ASIAN AMERICAN ARTS CENTRE - WEBSITE PROJECT, 2001-2004 (Box R3799)
    - 2001 CC 100 - AMERICANS FOR THE ARTS - JOINT CONVENTION, "PARTICIPATE 2001", 2001-2004 (Box R3799)
    - 2001 CC 101 - ART AND SCIENCE LABORATORY - AESTHETIC RESEARCH PROGRAM, 2000-2002 (Box R3799)
    - 2001 CC 103 - AMERICAN ASSEMBLY - NATIONAL ASSEMBLY ON "ARTS, TECHNOLOGY AND INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY", 2001-2002 (Box R3799)
    - 2001 CC 104 - AMERICAN COMPOSERS ORCHESTRA - ORCHESTRA TECHNOLOGY INITIATIVE, 2001-2004 (Box R3799)
- AC.2006.067: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 2001-2005; AC.2006.067; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3800-R3803.; 4 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3800-R3803.
  - Creativity and Culture (CC), AC.2006.067.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - 2001 CC 110 - UNIVERSITY OF MASSACHUSETTS (AMHERST) - "INTERSECTIONS Ill: FUTURE AESTHETICS", 2001-2003 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 112 - UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN (MADISON) - WORKSHOP AND MEETING, ''THE GENDERED DIMENS10NS OF AUTHORITARIAN LEGAGIES", 2001-2003 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 113 - OTHER MINDS - WEB RADIO/NET MUSIC INITIATIVE, 2001-2004 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 115 - ASIAN CINEVISION - CAPACITY-BUILDING INITIATIVE, 2001-2002 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 119 - MEDIA ARTS CENTER SAN DIEGO - DOCUMENTARY SERIES, "BEYOND THE DREAM: CALIFORNIA AND THE REDISCOVERY OF AMERICA", 2001-2002 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 121 - AARON DAVIS HALL, INC. - PERFORMANCE PIECE, "BROWN BUTTERFLY", 2001-2003 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 122 - AMERICAN COMPOSERS ORCHESTRA - "MIDNIGHT MOVIE", 2001-2003 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 123 - APPALS HOP - "FROM THE HOOD TO THE HOLLER", 2001-2003 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 126 - NORTHEASTERN UNIVERSITY - "ALL POWER TO THE PEOPLE", 2001-2004 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 127 - CENTER THEATRE GROUP - "THE CHAVEZ RAVINE PROJECT", 2001-2003 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 128 - CHILDREN'S THEATRE CO. - PLAY ABOUT EXPERIENCE OF SOMALI YOUTH IN AMERICA, 2001-2003 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 129 - CLEVELAND PUBLIC THEATRE - "BLUE SKY TRANSMISSION", 2001-2005 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 130 - CREATIVE TIME - "THE EAST NEW YORK PROJECT", 2001-2002 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 131 - CROSS PERFORMANCE, INC. - "THE GEOGRAPHY TRILOGY", 2001-2203 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 132 - DANCE THEATER WORKSHOP - "REPORT OF THE BODY", 2001-2003 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 133 - PING CHONG AND COMPANY - MOVEMENT THEATER WORK, "SHAOLIN 2002", 2001-2003 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 134 - BILL T. JONES/ARNIE ZANE DANCE CO. - SERIES OF NEW DANCE WORKS, 2001-2003 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 135 - FUND FOR WOMEN ARTISTS - "THE DOLL PLAYS", 2001-2003 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 136 - GALE GATES ET AL - "WINE-BLUE-OPEN-WATER", 2001-2005 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 137 - HERE - DANCE-THEATER WORK, "DEAD TECH", 2001-2002 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 138 - INTERSECTION FOR THE ARTS - "BLOOD IN THE BRAIN", 2001-2003 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 139 - JAZZ GALLERY - "SANGHA: COLLABORATIVE FABLES", 2001-2003 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 141 - UNIVERSITY OF ILLINOIS (URBANA-CHAMPAIGN) - "BEETHOVEN PROJECT", 2001-2002 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 142 - LOWER MANHATTAN CULTURAL COUNCIL - "SPECTROPIA", 2000-2003 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 143 - LYRIC OPERA CENTER FOR AMERICAN ARTISTS - "MORNING STAR", 2001-2002 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 144 - MABOU MINES - OPERA, "RED BEADS", 2001-2002 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 145 - MASSACHUSETTS MUSEUM OF CONTEMPORARY ART - PERFORMANCE PIECE, "THE DREAM LIFE OF BRICKS", 2001-2002 (Box R3800)
    - 2001 CC 146 - MAUI ARTS & CULTURAL CENTER - TRILOGY OF PLAYS, "WHEN WE WERE ONE", 2001-2003 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 147 - McCARTER THEATRE - "CROWNS", 2001-2002 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 148 - HOUSE FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - COLLABORATIVE MUSIC-THEATRE WORK, 2001-2003 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 149 - MUSEUM OF CONTEMPORARY ART - MUSIC-THEATRE WORK, "ZENO AT 4AM", 2001-2003 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 150 - MUSICAL TRADITIONS/PAUL DRESHER ENSEMBLE - "SOUND STAGE", 2001-2003 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 151 - ONTOLOGICAL-HYSTERIC THEATER - "TRANSCENDENTAL RACE CAR", 2001-2004 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 154 - RENNIE HARRIS PUREMOVEMENT- DANCE PIECE, "FACING MECCA", 2001-2003 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 155 - RUDE MECHANICALS - "THE MARFA PROJECT", 2001-2002 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 156 - SAN JOSE REPERTORY THEATRE - "LAS MENINAS", 2001-2002 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 157 - SAN JOSE TAIKO GROUP - "THE TRIANGLE PROJECT: HOMECOMING HOME", 2001-2003 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 158 - TAMAR ROGOFF PERFORMANCE PROJECTS - "DAUGHTER OF A PACIFIST", 2001-2002 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 159 - THEATREWORKS/USA - MUSICAL ABOUT RACIAL TOLERANCE, 2001-2003 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 160 - THEATER OFFENSIVE - "BEL CANTO", 2001-2004 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 161 - HEYWARD, JULIA - INTERACTIVE DVD, "MIRACLES IN REVERSE", 2001-2004 (Box R3801)
      Digital items have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
    - HEYWARD, JULIA - "MIRACLES IN REVERSE", 2006:067:001; Digital
    - 2001 CC 162 - OHIO STATE UNIVERSITY - PLAY BASED ON LIFE OF LEONARD BERNSTEIN, 2001-2003 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 163 - LOS ANGELES CHAMBER ORCHESTRA - NEW MUSICAL WORK, 2001-2002 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 164 - WOOSTER GROUP - THEATRICAL PRODUCTION, "AS I LAY DYING", 2001-2003 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 165 - YERBA BUENA CENTER FOR THE ARTS - "FROM OUR MOTHER", 2001-2003 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 166 - ASIAN IMPROV ARTS - "UP FROM THE ROOT!", 2001-2005 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 167 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (LOS ANGELES) - FESTIVAL INVESTIGATING "THE CLASSICS OF CHICANO THEATER", 2001-2004 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 170 - MUSEUM OF MODERN ART - "AFRICAN MUSEUM PROFESSIONALS WORKSHOP", 2001-2002 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 171 - UNIVERSITY OF UTAH - EXHIBITION, "UTAH'S FIRST NATIONS...", 2001-2003 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 172 - MEMORIA ABIERTA (ARGENTINA) - "REPRESENTATION AND PUBLIC CULTURE" PROJECT, 2000-2003 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 173 - NATIONAL AUTONOMOUS UNIVERSITY OF MEXICO - "MEXICAN CULTURE REPORT", 2001-2003 (Box R3801)
    - 2001 CC 175 - LA MORADA CORP. FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF WOMEN (CHILE) - PUBLICATION AND DISTRIBUTION OF REVISTA DE CRITICA CULTURAL, 2001-2003 (Box R3802)
    - 2001 CC 179 - CINE QUA NON, INC. - MEDIA CAPACITY-BUILDI NG INITIATIVE, 2001-2002 (Box R3802)
    - 2001 CC 192 - OMAHA THEATER CO. FOR YOUNG PEOPLE - "PRIDE PLAYERS PROJECT", 2001-2003 (Box R3802)
    - 2001 CC 199 - PRINCETON UNIVERSITY - MEASURING RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN THE ARTS AND COMMUNITY LIFE, 2001-2004 (Box R3802)
    - 2001 CC 202 - NATIONAL VIDEO RESOURCES - AFTER 9/11 VIDEO COLLECTION, 2001-2003 (Box R3802)
    - 2001 CC 203 - MEDIA ACCESS PROJECT - EFFECTS OF CONSOLIDATION OF RADIO STATION OWNERSHIP, 2001-2003 (Box R3802)
    - 2001 CC 208 - THE THING, INC. - DEVELOPING INDEPENDENT AND SUSTAINABLE MEDIA PROJECTS, 2001-2002 (Box R3802)
    - 2001 CC 209 - UNIVERSITY OF SOUTHERN DENMARK - "FORUM FOR DIALOGUE BETWEEN CIVILIZATIONS", 2001-2003 (Box R3802)
    - 2001 CC 211 - INDEPENDENT TELEVISION SERVICE - IMPACTS OF DIGITAL TECHNOLOGY, 2001-2003 (Box R3802)
    - 2001 CC 212 - LOWER MANHATTAN CULTURAL COUNCIL - REBUILDING ARTS IN DOWNTOWN AREA AFTER ATTACKS ON WORLD TRADE CENTER, 2001-2003 (Box R3802)
    - 2001 CC 213 - NATIONAL ASSOCIATI ON OF LATINO ARTS AND CULTURE - DOCUMENTARY, "VISIONES: LATINO ARTS AND CULTURE", 2001-2003 (Box R3802)
    - 2001 CC 214 - CIRCLE IN THE SQUARE THEATRE SCHOOL - OUTREACH ACTIVITIES, 2001-2003 (Box R3802)
    - 2001 CC 216 - CARIBBEAN CONTEMPORARY ARTS (TRINIDAD & TOBAGO) - AUDIENCE DEVELOPMENT, COMMUNITY OUTREACH AND INTRA-REGIONAL EXCHANGE INITIATIVES, 2001-2003 (Box R3802)
    - 2001 CC 222 - MIDDLEBURY COLLEGE - COLLOQUIA ON LATINO/CHICANO AND AFRICAN AMERICAN CULTURAL FORMS, 2001-2003 (Box R3802)
    - 2001 CC 225 - PUBLIC THEATER - "NEW WORKS DEVELOPMENT PROGRAMS", 2001-2003 (Box R3802)
    - 2001 CC 227 - INTERFAITH ALLIANCE FOUNDATION - CREATING CONGREGATIONAL PARTNERSHIPS, 2001-2004 (Box R3802)
    - 2001 CC 229 - WOMEN'S WORLD ORGANIZATION FOR RIGHTS, LITERATURE AND DEVELOPMENT - PROJECT ON GENDER-BASED CENSORSHIP, 2001-2003 (Box R3803)
    - 2001 CC 230 - MUSEUM OF MODERN ART - CELEBRATION OF 15TH YEAR OF RF FILM AND VIDEO FELLOWSHIPS, 2001-2003 (Box R3803)
    - 2001 CC 233 - NEW ENGLAND FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - CAMBODIAN ARTIST COMMUNITY RESIDENCY PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3803)
    - 2001 CC 233 - NEW ENGLAND FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - CAMBODIAN ARTIST COMMUNITY RESIDENCY PROGRAM - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 2000-2003 (Box R3803)
    - 2002 CC 006 - SEATTLE ART MUSEUM - EXHIBITION OF AFRICAN ART, 2001-2003 (Box R3803)
    - 2002 CC 006 - SEATTLE ART MUSEUM - EXHIBITION OF AFRICAN ART - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 2001-2003 (Box R3803)
    - 2002 CC 007 - HENRY ART GALLERY ASSOCIATION - EXHIBITION ON GENOMICS EFFECT ON CONTEMPORARY ART, 2001-2004 (Box R3803)
    - 2002 CC 010 - EARTHWAYS FOUNDATION - 2002 FESTIVAL OF SACRED MUSIC - LOS ANGELES, 2001-2002 (Box R3803)
    - Songs for the City of Angels; World Festivals of Sacred Music - Los Angeles, 2002; 2006:067:002; Digital
    - 2002 CC 023 - LIBRARY OF CONGRESS - "SAVE OUR SOUNDS" PROJECT, 2001-2003 (Box R3803)
- AC.2006.069: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1982-2003; AC.2006.069; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, Box R3804.; 1 standard record storage box, Box R3804.
  - Creativity and Culture (CC), AC.2006.069.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2002 CC 048 - BROOKLYN ACADEMY OF MUSIC - NEXT WA, 1982-2003; 6 folders. (Box R3804)
- AC.2006.076: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1998-2005; AC.2006.076; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3811-R3815.; 5 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3811-R3815.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - RESIDENT (Abel, Elizabeth), 1999-2000 (Box R3811)